Everything went pretty smoothly after
we defeated the Labyrinth Stratum Lord,
and two days later, we finally
made it out of the maze.
How come everything
around here is so empty?
It's cause outside the occasional hunter,
people rarely come to this stratum.
The facilities are specifically for
hunters, so they're rather barebones.
Ah, that makes sense.
But I don't see any walls put up,
so how do they protect
themselves from monster attacks?
Outside of the maze,
the rest of the stratum is a wasteland
where not even monsters can survive.
Wow.
There are many aspects of the
dungeon that are still unknown to us,
despite years of research,
most pressing of which is the recent
resurgence of stratum lords we've been seeing.
I can't help but think it's
an ill omen of things to come.
I guess encountering two
stratum lords back to back would
be nearly impossible under
normal circumstances we finally
made it the Labyrinth
Stratum's Hunters
Association
oh
director Bami I didn't expect
to see to keep back so soon.
My goodness.
I know you're bored,
but surely there has to be something
around here that needs organizing.
Of course, sorry about that, sir.
Huh, so Director Bear's
real name is Balmy.
Surprisingly cute, but
that doesn't matter.
He's always gonna be Director Bear to me.
You've all been through quite a lot.
Get some rest, we'll talk more tomorrow.
After finally reuniting with everyone
and finding a safe place to rest,
I fell asleep for the first time since
falling into the labyrinth stratum.
The song of the day is an animal.
I am so happy that I'm not frozen!
I am so happy about this song?
Why?
And if you want me to play
I love you, I love you
I love you, it's true
How many times do you know?
Thank you.
All right, then, we'll leave
the rest to you. See ya!
We're staying here for
a little bit longer.
Because Director Bear asked us to survey
the perimeter of the giant labyrinth!
Excuse me, my name is Mishuel.
Check it out, Hulemy.
The guy who just walked in is
super handsome, don't you think?
Uh, yeah, no kidding.
About the map.
Right.
Would you mind coming back in three days?
We're in the middle of updating our
maps with the most current information.
Yes, I understand.
In that case, I'll return another time.
Come back soon.
We'll be waiting.
there it is behold the hottie
effect he looked exactly
how i imagine a gallant
hero out of a fairy tale
would if you ask me that
stereotype has been blown
way out of proportion i
mean just think of all the
famous hunters you've heard
about most of them are
either grizzled middle-aged
dudes or covered in muscles
you know oh no you're right
but not all of them what
about the hunter called
she of a hundred blessings
and divine favor you
remember her right according
to all of the stories i've
heard about her she was
super duper beautiful i
want to be a hunter like her
one day yeah i suppose
there are exceptions to the
rule by all accounts her
beauty was unmatched and
she was not only strong but
kind to everyone a perfect
person who knows maybe
that pretty boy is destined
to have his name carved
into the history books too.
If he's strong enough to challenge the
stratum by himself, he must be quite good.
I heard there weren't
many people around here.
That's the only reason I
came. Oh man. What's with him?
He's got this totally different
kind of depressed vibe now.
Hottie?
More like definitely not.
I was so nervous I wanted to throw up.
I don't get why everybody
stares at me like that.
It's scary.
Wait a sec.
Are you telling me this is the real him?
I can't take this kind
of pressure anymore.
I keep talking to people.
I wish everybody would
just leave me alone.
So he's actually really
bad at communicating,
and to hide it, he's completely
assumed this hot guy persona?
He's suddenly a lot more
relatable. Stop that.
Mom would always scold me whenever I'd
start to wallow in these negative thoughts.
I gotta be positive.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Now I kind of want to help this guy out.
I remember reading somewhere
that chocolate has compounds
in it that help people relax
and feel less stressed.
Hello there.
Please insert coins.
Mmm.
It's so sweet and delicious.
I'm feeling a lot more calm now, too.
What a fantastic magic item.
Plus, I'm not dealing with a person, so
buying things here isn't nerve-wracking.
Right.
Tomorrow I'll negotiate.
What does that mean?
Is he going to try to buy me from Llamas?
Boxo! Mr.
Mishuel said he wanted to accompany us
on our assignment from Director Bear.
Oh, that's what he meant
when he said negotiation?
Thanks a lot for tagging along,
but what about your own quest?
Will you have time to finish it?
But of course.
I'm cool with it.
We've got yet another capable
hunter in our party now.
He seems reliable.
But of course.
Well, I for one am super happy
you wanted to come with us.
It's not every day we get a chance
to travel with the aloof Black Flash.
Ha-ha-ha, but of course.
Come on, Mishuel.
You gotta change up your
responses a little, dude.
You sound like an NPC.
I was wondering,
Hulemy, how long is it going to take us to
make it all the way around the labyrinth?
Based off the pictures, Boxotug, I'd say
it'll take us no more than three weeks.
What do you think, Mishuel?
Ha-ha-ha, but of course. Huh?
I'll be in the rear to make sure
we don't get attacked from behind!
Fine! Sure.
There go the communication issues again.
But I've been paying close attention
to him while we've been walking.
My personal goal for this month,
learn to act natural around strangers.
All I have to do is be nice and relaxed.
That shouldn't be too difficult, right?
So that's the reason
he decided to join us.
He's trying his best to improve
his crippling social anxiety.
I was really nervous,
traveling with two beauties, and the band
of gluttons are all so cute I want to die.
The only thing I could do was keep
a straight face and not stare.
Everyone insisted that we go to sleep
and let Boxxo take care of keeping watch.
I still can't believe this magic item
has a mind of its own. Hello there!
I'm sorry, good evening to you!
Um, excuse me.
Everything's gonna be fine.
You know it's funny, shopping
usually stresses me out.
Yup, one of the vending machine's
many advantages is its accessibility.
And so a week went by
without the barest hint
of fighting and the days
were quiet and peaceful.
But today there seemed to be
something that was bothering Lamas.
Hey Lamas.
Did you not get enough sleep last night?
If you're feeling under the weather,
you and Boxo can come right on the car.
Hello there.
Oh don't worry about me.
I'm doing just fine.
I couldn't be feeling any better.
Wait a second, Lamas.
Don't overexert yourself.
You should take breaks when you need to.
Oh, shit.
Careful.
That was close.
Nice one, Mishuel.
Hulemy.
Could you look after her?
Of course, no problem.
Alright, first let's get
you out of those clothes!
I'm okay.
Give me just a second
and I'll do it myself.
Don't try to play the hero when
you're on the verge of collapse.
You have to learn to accept
kindness when it's offered.
As usual, you stubbornly try to
push yourself past your limits.
Huh?
Was she sick or something?
At times like this, you've got
to rest, not power through it.
Okay.
That's right.
Llamas sometimes has off days
like this, about once every month.
I should have picked up on it faster.
What's going on?
Could it be that she's hungry?
Suco, do you know?
I've heard about this
happening with humans
and a bunch of other monkey-like species.
Their women have this thing where they'll
occasionally bleed from
their private parts.
I wish there was something
I could do to help.
Huh?
Boxo, what's up with you?
If you've transformed, then that must mean
you came up with some kind of plan, then.
Uh how are we supposed to use this the
cloth has a strange feel to it or is it
paper wait Maybe it's absorbing it all so
quickly i see this will come in handy it's
not something i'd normally Think about you
see a ton of female adventurers and all
sorts of fantasy media but in real life
You've got to deal with this kind of thing.
Hello there.
Oh, this is great.
I want to take this for a spin.
So the first load is on me.
It's been over two weeks since we
set out to survey the perimeter.
According to Hulami's estimations,
we should be able to return to the
Labyrinth Stratum Village in three days.
After the incident with Lamas, Mishwa
started hanging out with everyone more often.
He's adjusting pretty well.
Yep.
Boxxo is a truly
outstanding magic item, huh?
You got that right.
His food and drinks are super tasty
and he has all sorts of useful tools.
On top of that, he even protects us.
I've been studying magic
items for a long time now,
and I've never heard of any artifact like
Boxxo showing up in the dungeon before.
You don't say.
What's up, Mikenne?
Stop the cart, now!
Can you smell something, pal?
Yeah, I smell it, too.
There's a faint scent of humans
coming from further up ahead.
Four or five of them, I'd say.
I can't make out what
they're saying from here,
but from the base in their
voices, it sounds like men I see,
what the hell's going on?
There shouldn't be any
hunters in a place like this
I'm starting to get a bad
feeling about this situation.
Forgive me, everybody, but there's a good
chance these people have come here for me!
It was never my intention to
drag you into my problems,
so please let me face them alone.
We don't know if it's you they're after?
Besides, even if they are, we
can't just let you go by yourself.
You don't understand.
If you guys follow me, your
lives will be in danger.
Hold on a second.
Before we decide anything,
mind telling us who these people
are and why they're after you?
His communication issues were a little
rough, but they were manageable.
This secretiveness, on the
other hand, is a problem.
I totally get that you're
concerned about us getting hurt.
But trust me, we'll be fine.
With Boxo by our side, there's no way
things will go wrong. Hello there!
It'll be easier to show him.
Where did this blue light come from?
It's called a barrier.
It's Boxo's blessing.
If this barrier can
withstand an attack from you,
would it put your mind at ease
about letting us come along?
Very well but if I can breach his
defenses will you promise that
you won't follow after me no matter
what we promise all right then I
won't hold anything
back
bring
it
you can throw whatever you want at
the barrier I know it'll block it
come on barrier I'm counting on you.
It didn't work?
Points reduced by 500.
Whoa, holy crap!
The Crocodile Stratum Lord's Body
Slam took 1,000 points when it hit me.
You're saying this was
half as strong as that?
Yeah, way to go, Boxo! Hello
there! See? Everyone's okay.
And that's why you don't have
to worry about us getting hurt.
What she said.
Understood.
We'll be counting on you if things
go south, Boxo. Hello there!
Lamas, the five humans are
just ahead. He's right.
Three of their number are
probably highly skilled swordsmen.
As for the remaining two,
they most likely employ
the power of blessings
or cast magic spells of the four elements.
You can sense all that from this far away?
That's really impressive.
Well, it's not much help here.
You must be Mr. Mishel.
What an honor it will
be to claim your life.
As I suspected.
Tell me, who hired you?
Ha!
I'm certain you already
have at least some idea.
Fair enough.
By the way, are the beast person and
the girl carrying that box your friends?
They're both strangers.
We happened to take the same job.
I don't care if you come after
me, but if you attack them,
you won't live to regret it.
Wow, he's so cool!
I see.
Very well, then.
I hereby swear we won't
lay a single finger on
them as long as you
surrender without resisting.
I'm supposed to believe that?
I'm afraid you don't
have any other choice.
So, what is your decision, Mr. Mishuel?
I have another option!
If I defeat all of you, you won't
even have a chance to hurt them!
How commendable of you.
You've got a warrior's
heart that much is certain,
and so we will grant
you a warrior's death.
Lamas, be careful. Right.
Here's hoping my barrier can
block magic attacks, too.
Great!
Lamas, time to go ham on these jerks.
What?
A blessing that controls water?
It's not strong enough to
cause any real injuries,
but it's enough to block your view.
Why don't you choke on some car
wash soap while you're at it?
What is this stuff?
I got some of it in my eyes!
It burns!
I can't see!
Good luck hitting anything with your
magic while you have soap in your eyes.
Now it's time for rinse mode.
Oh!
It hurts so bad!
Mr. Mishuel!
We're done over here!
Thanks for your help.
If you weren't here, things
could have gotten dangerous.
Huh?
Of course it wasn't a problem.
Could you go fetch the others?
I still have a fair bit of information
I need to get out of these guys.
Sure, you got it.
We'll be back with Hulemy
and the others right away!
It looks like Mishuel's got
a lot going on with him.
It might be best if we don't
pry too much into his business.
Hello there!
I apologize for involving
you in my personal matters.
Don't worry about it.
Boxo's pulled me into
plenty of trouble by getting
kidnapped and then falling
into a stratum split,
so I'm used to it.
You got that right. Too bad.
Sorry, and thanks for
always coming to my rescue.
I'm afraid I can't tell you any details,
but as you can see, my life is
being targeted by assassins.
If we continue to travel together,
your lives will be put in danger again?
so I'll be transferring
to another stratum.
I appreciate everything
you've done to help me.
Wait, I have an idea!
Instead of traveling alone, why don't
you join the Menagerie of Fools?
They'd welcome you.
The captain mentioned before he was
looking for new talented hunters.
Yeah, I remember he was
going on and on about that.
I almost wanted to punch him in
the mouth to make him shut up.
He said, as long as they're
strong, who cares about their past?
Pretty much everyone here
is in some kind of mess.
Wait, I've heard of them before.
Aren't they a really
famous group of hunters?
Yep, that's right.
We take on jobs with them
every once in a while.
They're all such kind
and interesting people.
Also, just talk to them about it.
Don't go overthinking it, okay?
All right, then.
I'll reach out to them
as soon as I get back.
Maybe one day we'll work together again.
I don't know anyone in the menagerie.
You want me to talk to
a bunch of strangers?
I can't handle something like that!
It's a good day, but it's a special day.
I'd like to be a happy day.
I don't know what's going on.
But I don't know what's going on.
This moment is a happiness.
Today is one day, always.
After finishing Director Bear's request,
we finally made our way back up
to the Clear Flow Lake Stratum.
Wait, what are you talking about?
I could have sworn I
saw Voxo doing business
here in the village just over a week ago.
Huh?
It seems I've got a couple
of impersonators now
and they're set up where
Chain's restaurant used
to be a silver coin was
inserted wait a sec what
kind of magic item coughs
thank you very much
this tastes exactly like the food
Chain's restaurant used to serve
and so we put two and two together it was
all a setup Chain's
restaurant placed those
fake vending machines in order to try to
steal customers the next
day I started selling
my wares again and what do you know before
the week was up all the
fake vending machines
went out of business thank you very much
I look forward to serving you again Amen.